MY BIAS, MY BOSS
D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X!
D.N.X! D.N.X!
Someone once said
that love is like a traffic accident,
striking without warning.
Back then, I had no idea
that I was about to get starstruck
for the next 12 years.
Seventeen.
What saved me from my loneliness
was his music.
- Let's see the final results.
- Please, please, please.
This week's number one is
D.N.X!
My fan activity brought me friends
when I was lonely.
It helped me discover talents
I never knew I had.
TO THE DNX CONCERT!
YOU CAN DO IT! SEE CHAN!
Most of all, I felt alive.
And I was happy.
But to him, I was
just one light in a sea of many.
D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X!
D.N.X! D.N.X! D.N.X!
10 YEARS LATER
ALWAYS ON CHANI'S SIDE
D.N.X
So, I made a decision.
I would get close to him.
My dream is to become a successful fan.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPISODE 1
This event will not only include
our top VVIP clients,
but also our key overseas partners,
and members of the press.
Through our world-class
brand partnerships,
we aim to present the future of Korea's
premium fashion market.
The event will be held
at the S Convention Event Hall.
Um, uh...
Nam Da-reum, do you have something to say?
The waiting area there is a little
insufficient for a large number of people.
I was wondering
what the plan was for that...
That is not your concern, Nam Da-reum.
The event team will take care of it.
Just do as you are told.
Yes.
- That is all.
- There he goes again, first thing.
He is so exhausting.
He acts like he owns the place.
Wish he'd be quiet.
He is making everyone miserable.
Seriously.
SE CORPORATION
ENTER A SEARCH TERM. RESIGNATION LETTER
If I
said I am quitting my job,
my mom would flip out, right?
The second your mom handed out
those rice cakes
to celebrate, you were dead meat.
I heard she hung a banner for you
at the neighborhood entrance.
APPELLO
But.
Chan always said,
"Unframe," to break free from the mold.
I... If I get in tomorrow...
I will get in, right?
Or maybe not?
No. Even if I do not get in,
I will try again.
I am going to work at APPELLO,
no matter what.
But are you not breaking too free?
You worked hard for that big company.
There, I just feel
like a cog in the machine.
Nothing I do makes my heart race.
Then what about APPELLO?
It is like a group
that is just debuting, you know?
Think of all the work there will be to do.
The kind of company
that could really change
if they just hired
one good employee like me.
Yeah, right. Chan is the one
making your heart race.
Anyway! Just look.
Look! Look!
Just let me get into APPELLO.
I'll become a legend in fashion marketing,
and build it into a towering success.
I...
I will be his favorite employee.
I have to get this job. Let's do this!
- Go for it!
- Go for it!...
Go for it!
YOUVERSE, YOU HAVE A NEW NOTIFICATION
LEE CHAN
LISTENING TO D.N.X'S DEBUT ALBUM.
YOU SHOULD TOO!
2015: IDOL GROUP D.N.X DEBUTS.
NAM DA-REUM BECOMES A FIRST-TIME STAN!
2017: D.N.X DISBANDS. BUT I'M STILL A FAN
2018: LEE CHAN OF D.N.X
BEGINS HIS ACTING CAREER
2019: LEE CHAN OPENS
FASHION BOUTIQUE 'APPELLO'
2022: BEST NEW ACTOR
AND FASHION PLATFORM CEO
LEE CHAN'S GOLDEN AGE
LEE CHAN IS THE TREND
LEE CHAN'S APPELLO IS A MUST-TRY
HE'S TAKING OVER FASHION.
HE DOESN'T FOLLOW, HE LEADS
HE IS 'CAREER GOALS'
YOU CAN COUNT ON LEE CHAN
THAT'S LEE CHAN FOR YOU
BRILLIANT LEE CHAN
Is he even human?
Just you wait.
I'll be there soon.
APPELLO:
SUCCESSFUL APPLICANTS ANNOUNCED AT 2 PM
SE CORPORATION
SE CORPORATION AND APPELLO:
INVESTMENT AND PARTNERSHIP MEETING
How old is the CEO?
Well, I heard he's only
in his early thirties.
- Early thirties?
- Yes.
Wow, he's just a kid.
STRATEGIC INVESTMENT
AND PARTNERSHIP PROPOSAL
SE CORPORATION
Sir, let's go.
A pleasure to meet you.
I'm Kang Ha-gi from APPELLO.
APPELLO DUE DILIGENCE REQUEST LIST
Provide the materials, and we'll give
your investment a positive review.
- What about the NDA?
- I'm establishing a separate corporation,
so that's not possible right now.
That corporation wouldn't happen to be
a fashion platform just like ours,
would it?
I'm not sure what you're implying...
We're aiming for a
Fashion Platform Launch,
to provide a customized
shopping experience for our users.
Our core strategy is
Real-time review-based curation.
The existing method is...
It sounds like the room next door is busy
preparing for a Fashion Platform Launch.
Customized AI Styling,
Real-time review-based curation.
Wasn't all of that in the document
we gave you?
That was from our last due diligence...
I believe SE sent someone
to review it, yes.
Sheesh.
All the trends are the same these days.
There's no point in negotiating
if you start with accusations.
You can copy trends,
but you can't copy a philosophy.
There's nothing more to discuss.
We won't take your investment.
This industry is smaller than you think.
If you just walk out on the deal
like this,
You can't handle the consequences.
It seems your attempt
to steal our key information has failed.
Worry about your contract renewal,
Director Kim.
There's really no turning back now.
My resignation has been processed.
And I've packed all my things.
Please, APPELLO.
Please hire me. Please, please hire me.
It's the 59th minute.
I'm so nervous.
APPELLO RECRUITMENT VIEW RESULTS
NAME: NAM DA-REUM
NAME: NAM DA-REUM, DATE OF BIRTH: 19991127
CHECK APPLICATION STATUS
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE
CONGRATULATIONS! NAM DA-REUM,
YOU PASSED THE 2025 RECRUITMENT
Oh my gosh, I really got in!
CEO, you were so impressive back there.
You can't copy our philosophy.
You know this is no time for jokes, right?
Check the security of
all internal documents.
Right.
Mom!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What's with her?
I made it!
CEO, this--
No, no, we got a clear shot of her face.
Right here, look.
- Here.
- Damn...
Thank you, goodbye!
- Did you really get in?
- I got in.
I'm going to
APPELLO!
In my childhood dreams
I go away to find my lost self.
Beyond the blue sky,
spread the wings inside me.
Embrace the dream that's gone,
another way of mine.
NEIGHBORHOOD
So, what does it feel like
to become an icon of an era?
The man who achieved that difficult feat
is right here.
The legendary group that shook up
the K-pop scene...
Hey, Chani must be busy.
- Created a syndrome...
- He's been out of the picture.
Well, I'm even busier.
Hurry up and eat so we can go.
This guy doesn't have an ounce
of Feeling in him.
People need to rest when they can!
Idiot.
Let's go, let's go.
In my childhood dreams
Hey, you can do it like this.
This is how Chan did it.
- No, you do it like this.
- Hello!
I'm not going. I can't go.
This must be destiny.
I've found her, my ideal type.
What should we get?
Here he goes again.
Excuse me!
Yes!
This is for you, since you're a regular.
Thank you so much.
Oh, your friend must live nearby.
- Hey, who's this?
- How did you get here?
By bus.
Well, for the ride home,
why don't you and I get something started?
Excuse me?
Your friend?
- Hurry and have a seat.
- Okay.
Okay.
How about I show you a magic trick?
Sure.
Okay, watch this.
Oh, no!
And if I do this...
For my next trick...
A heart for Chan.
By any chan-ce, am I a bother?
A trick where it sticks.
A trick where it falls.
It sticks and falls. Sticks and falls.
It's simply chan-tastic!
Goodbye. Farewell, my love. Chan Chan.
My apologies.
Lee Chan...
What am I going to do...
You scared me!
If I had just gotten his poster
today would have been perfect.
Lee Chan.
I thought the vibe was pretty good.
What do girls even see
in that jerk Lee Chan?
He used to be a total outcast and a loser.
An outcast and a loser.
An outcast and a loser,
an outcast and a loser.
An outcast and a loser.
An outcast?
A loser?
Here she goes again.
I have to stop her. Crap.
People have no idea about that guy's past.
- Was it you?
- Huh?
Making Lee Chan an outcast
and bullying him
that was you, wasn't it? You.
I'll never forgive you!
Ugh...
We're so sorry!
We're sorry.
- My friend's having a hard time, and--
- ...
- Life's just been so hard for her...
- He deserved it.
She has this, uh, chronic condition...
anger management issues.
We're truly very sorry.
We're really, really so sorry.
What's there to be sorry about?
I'm not sorry at all.
Bullies are the worst.
Do you have any idea how that feels?
Mom!
We're sorry.
Do you?
Ow, ow, ow...
My friend, she's willing
to get on her knees to...
She wants to beg for forgiveness.
She's clearly very remorseful. Right?
- Yes.
Well...
That's enough. You can go.
Oh, you're so incredibly generous.
No, I, I...
You should head inside.
You. You!
Hey, let go of me!
What?
Anger management issues
from not being able to find a job?
Someone who works at SE?
Do you know her?
Never seen her before in my life.
I know.
I should've got her number.
Hey, hurry, hurry!
Hey, wait. Oh, hold on.
Throw her! Wow, geez. Ah! Oh, man.
- Oh, man.
- Ugh, she's heavy.
Hey, what the... Geez.
She weighs twice as much when she's drunk.
Seriously. Geez.
Wow, I can't believe... Ugh.
Hey.
Wow, but for real, our Nam Da-reum
is actually becoming a successful fan.
But do you think Chan knows?
It's been ten years since DNX disbanded.
That a fan from the Stone Age like her
still exists?
I know, right?
Hey, let's go too.
Okay.
Hey, wait, hold on.
Seriously, go.
SEONGJU STATION
SEONGJU
APPELLO
- Which department did you join?
- Oh, uh, I'm in the MD Team.
Um...
Oh, I'm in the Marketing Team.
- Marketing? I'm in the Marketing Team too.
- Oh, really?
Let's get along. I'm Park Youngwoo.
- And your name is...?
- Oh, my name is Lee Min-a.
- Ah, Min-a.
- Ms. Lee Min-a.
Oh, I'm Nam Da-reum.
Ms. Nam Da-reum.
So you're "one of a kind."
Ah, yes. I get it.
Let's all get along.
"Love for your peers
is love for your country,"
- as they say, right? How about a cheer?
- Oh, sounds good.
Are you all friends already?
Congratulations on becoming part of
the APPELLO family.
I'll be in charge of
your orientation today.
I'm Kim Mi-young,
the manager of the Marketing Team.
And these are your employee ID cards.
- Mr. Youngwoo.
- Yes, thank you.
- Ms. Min-a.
- Thank you.
And Ms. Da-reum.
Thank you.
APPELLO currently has 82 employees.
As of today, there are three new recruits.
Then that means there are only 85
of these ID cards in the whole world.
It's basically limited edition
merch from Chan.
And it's even customized.
All right, shall we begin
the proper company introduction now?
- Let's go.
- Yes.
- This way.
Huh?
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
It's so clean and pretty.
- Ah, Ms. Min-a.
- Ah.
Most of the brands at APPELLO
are primarily online.
So we run a pop-up showroom
on the first floor
for them to meet customers.
We also have spaces for our brands,
like sewing rooms, pattern rooms,
and studios.
Oh, and as you can see,
the dress code is casual.
Starting tomorrow, you can wear
whatever fits your style,
whether it's a swimsuit or a party dress.
Wow.
This is the studio where we shoot
lookbooks and campaigns.
You could say all of APPELLO's
visual content comes from here.
The Marketing Team and the MD Team
are on the fourth floor.
Oh, and the CEO's office.
- Lastly, let's go say hello to the CEO.
- What?
- Right now?
- Yes.
Hello. I'm the new employee, Nam Da-reum.
That's so cheesy.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Nam Da-reum.
- I'm Nam Da-reum.
You sound like a call center.
Just be normal.
And don't get nervous in front of Chan.
Here, my secret weapon.
They say this Herbal Calming Pill
helps with the nerves.
Herbal Calming Pill... Her...
Don't worry. Don't worry.
I will send you the final proposal
by tomorrow morning.
Thank you. Thank you.
CEO.
These are our new employees.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm a new employee! I'm Park Youngwoo.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, I'm the new employee, Lee Min-a!
That's me.
Nice to meet you.
Chan?
What? Huh? Why is it someone else?
I'm Nam Da-reum.
NAM DA-REUM
A sincere welcome to APPELLO.
My office door is always open,
so you're welcome anytime.
Don't be formal.
Please treat me as a colleague.
Let's do great things together.
- Yes!
All right, I think that's all.
Shall we head out?
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
It's him.
Ms. Nam Da-reum.
Da-reum, what's wrong?
Are you okay? Hey, breathe!
- Call 911.
- Can't she breathe? What's wrong?
- Something's in her throat.
- She's choking.
Try to breathe like this,
breathe, breathe...
- What's wrong?
- Try to take a breath!
Try to take a breath, breathe.
Oh my! Oh my!
Da-reum...
Are you okay?
She'll be all right now.
I don't know what she ate, though.
- No...
- What is this?
What is this?
Take care.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, scoop, scoop!
Hey, guys, did you hear?
They say the new hire, Nam Da-reum,
caused a huge scene on her first day.
Seriously, a rookie causing trouble
on her first day.
What?
Mr. Lee Jin-sang?
Oops.
My mistake.
Get back to work.
I threw up on Director Lee Chan's pants
at my first company dinner.
Anyone can make mistakes
when they're nervous.
So don't worry about it too much.
Thank you, Ms. Kim.
Um, but...
Wasn't Lee Chan supposed to be the CEO?
They used to be co-CEOs.
But it recently changed
to a single-CEO system.
Then...
Director Lee Chan is only in charge
of fashion directing
for APPELLO's major events.
I see.
- So? So? You finally saw him in person?
- You weren't nervous, right?
- ...
- Looks like you cried. Totally moved?
We have to throw a party.
You're a successful fan!
- What do you want to eat?
- Deal, deal, deal.
Today, let's eat whatever
Da-reum wants to eat.
- Deal!
- Deal! Deal!
Deal!
Guys.
At Chan's company,
Chan isn't there.
Huh? That's like a push-up bra
with no push.
That one has 4 cm of super padding.
- It'll really fill you out.
- Yes. In that case, can I get every color?
And on top of that...
- Huh?
- On my first day, a CEO hugged me.
What?
What kind of... plot twist is this?
I'm so screwed!
So you're telling me that
the person who face-planted
on the CEO's chest was Nam Da-reum?
And the fact that she's from
SE Corporation, especially now.
It feels really sketchy, doesn't it?
If she'd put that on her resume,
even I wouldn't have hired her.
LEVEL/SCORE, L1, L2, 950, L1
I don't see why she'd go out of her way
to work for APPELLO.
CEO, you don't think she's a corporate spy
sent by Director Kim, do you?
From what I've heard, that guy...
has taken over countless companies
by planting spies.
Let's keep a close eye on her for now.
2025 E-COMMERCE LEADERS MEET-UP
You have to admit,
APPELLO is really smart.
While everyone was busy trying
to recruit famous designers,
they went after up-and-coming designers.
It was Director Lee Chan's idea.
He thought it was a shame that
talented brands were disappearing
because they lacked distribution networks.
So, did you two know each other
before all this?
We were high school classmates.
So you're best friends.
No wonder you'd entrust the company
to him.
Well, we'll be counting on you.
It seems SE Corporation has now joined
the e-commerce business as well.
We're scheduled to launch
a fashion platform soon.
Oh, so you're competing with APPELLO?
Oh, competition?
That's for those in the same weight class.
With our capital and distribution network,
if we don't take the number one spot,
that would be stranger, wouldn't it?
So you used investment as an excuse
to steal our data,
afraid you couldn't become number one?
I heard you've planted spies
and stolen secrets
from more than just one or two companies.
A spy?
Then what about APPELLO?
Do I have someone on the inside or not?
You're CEO Kang Ha-gi, aren't you?
I'm Do Eun-yong reporter
from the Insight Economic Times.
DO EUN-YONG, INSIGHT TIMES
A pleasure.
I look forward to favorable articles.
You should make some time
for an interview.
There's a lot I'm curious about.
If you contact my office,
we can coordinate.
I'm not interested in APPELLO.
I'm interested in you.
- I'm here. See you in a bit.
- I'm sorry. Something's come up.
Are you finished?
Why are you so dressed up?
- Did you put on cologne, too? Huh?
- Stop being so clingy.
What? I'm just happy to see you.
It's been a while.
You only call me when it's about work.
Why are you at a hotel
when you have a perfectly good home?
Someone keeps showing up.
Be careful.
- Don't be an owner risk.
- It's already over.
She was in the same industry.
Keep it that way.
Only get involved with people
who have as much to lose as you do.
That's our CEO Kang Ha-gi for you.
This is why you haven't dated anyone
in ten years...
No, wait. It's because you can't.
You're so cold.
Hey, get a hobby.
Or get into some fan activity.
I have a bias.
You do? Who?
- APPELLO.
- Yeah, yeah. I know.
Your bias is me. Say it's me.
Just say it's me. Say, 'Lee Chan'.
- Say, 'My bias is Lee Chan.'
- APPELLO.
Say, 'You're my bias.'
- Lee Chan.
- APPELLO.
- I'm gonna bite you.
That explains it.
- What's with her again?
- Just leave her.
Hey, Da-reum! Come have some chicken!
No!
I'm not done yet!
Hey, Mi-mi.
Can I just do another hundred of these?
I need to tire myself out so I don't think
about what happened in the CEO's office...
Great, it came back to me again.
What are you worried about?
Things like that happen.
No.
Hey, how am I supposed
to face the CEO now?
And what about being
the weird girl at work?
It's just your first day.
Just focus on doing a good job
from now on.
That'll make the rumors go away.
- You think so?
- Of course.
Besides, you're just a new employee.
How often will you even see the CEO?
Just avoid him.
Right?
I probably won't have
to see the CEO, right?
- Probably not.
- Nope.
Whew. Right. I won't.
I won't. I won't.
I just need to work hard and fix my image.
And the CEO...
I'll just avoid him.
Yes!
APPELLO X TUNZI POP-UP/SHOWROOM
OPENS IN NOVEMBER
This is our first pop-up
since launching TUNZI,
so let's all make sure
we're well prepared.
Yes!
I'll do it!
Let me help you with that!
I'll take that.
TUNZI OUTFIT SETUP LIST
Doors closing.
Work hard and avoid the CEO.
Hello! We're the new employees.
I'm Nam Da-reum,
- Park Youngwoo,
- and Lee Min-a!
We look forward to working with you!
- They're cute.
- They have good energy.
- Alright, cheers.
- Okay, okay.
Cheers!
We'll do our best!
Cheers! Cheers!
Cheers! We'll do our best!
Thank you.
Make way for CEO Kang Ha-gi!
Hello, CEO!
Hello, CEO.
- Please have a seat.
- CEO, please sit here.
No, no. Why here? Why this seat?
Please sit.
- I thought you were too busy to make it.
- I have to leave soon.
I have a video meeting
with an overseas VC.
- CEO, would you like a drink?
- A video conference.
That's right. Yes.
Help yourselves.
What's wrong? Why the somber mood?
Come on, everyone! Drink up! Huh?
Our CEO is here,
so let's get this party...
- Let's liven things up! Bottoms up!
- Bottoms up!
Um, CEO. You're not drinking?
- Please teach us well.
- We'll learn a lot from you.
Let's wrap this up early today.
Don't make the new hires drink too much.
Okay.
Da-reum has a company dinner tonight,
and I'm worried sick.
She doesn't know how to say no
and accepts every drink.
She's a born goody-two-shoes.
Anyway, that Da-reum...
Her problem is that she tries too hard.
- Man, seriously.
- Manager, have a drink.
Me? Me, me, me, me? Me, me, me.
Wow, Da-reum. I didn't know
you had this hidden talent.
Oh, my friends taught me.
You've got good friends.
Hold on a second, sweetie.
You have to accept my drink.
Okay.
- Here you go.
- Ms. Nam Da-reum.
Yes?
Have a drink from me instead.
Yes!
- But...
- Yes.
Use that glass.
Yes.
Okay.
These dinners are optional.
You can go home early if you're tired.
Yes, I understand.
Maybe I should go recharge for a bit.
Bottoms up, bottoms up!
It's almost time for my meeting,
so I'll be leaving now.
Yes, you should get going, CEO.
Take care, CEO.
Why is Director Kim here...?
Damn it...
If I keep working hard, someday...
I'll be able to see it for real, right?
But this looks amazing.
I have to take a picture.
Where is it?
Why isn't it working?
Zero, nine, one, six.
But that's his birthday.
Zero, nine, one...
Ms. Nam Da-reum.
Yes?
What are you doing here right now?
- CEO?
- Why are you here and not at the dinner?
Huh?
Me? Me?
I...
Oh, I was just trying to recharge a bit.
- Recharge?
- But you said...
...I'm always welcome.
That the CEO's office door is
always open.
And...
...a picture.
I was just going to take
one quick picture and leave.
What picture?
All right! Okay, everyone!
Attention, attention!
It's a rite of passage for every
new employee at our company.
- Oh, that?
- Yes.
Now, for our dear Lee Min-a...
Will it be CEO Ha-gi's faction,
or Director Chan's Faction?
Excuse me?
Team CEO Ha-gi, who's dependable
but a bit prickly,
hard on the outside, soft on the inside?
Or Team Director Chan,
who looks like he walked straight out
of a comic book?
Oh, um, I feel a little put on the spot...
Well, if you're that uncomfortable,
there's always Team Jin-sang.
- You can join.
- What?
- Hey, don't ruin the mood.
Hurry up and pick one.
Then I choose...
Team CEO Ha-gi?
- Min-a, nice! I'm on Team Ha-gi too.
- I knew it would be Ha-gi.
Why is everyone on Team Ha-gi?
Did she really come in here
drunk or something?
CEO Kang, that was a
very impressive presentation.
Well, Mr. Kang. APPELLO's growth is great,
Your platform's growth metrics
are outstanding.
Above all, the "Unframe" philosophy,
and the Unframe philosophy?
It's an excellent differentiator
in a very competitive market.
In what is a very crowded market.
Our team will be in touch within the week,
to discuss the next steps.
It's a pleasure, Mr. Kang.
- A pleasure, CEO Kang.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- I hope to see you again soon.
- You bet. Of course. Take care.
She didn't hear that, right?
Nam Da-reum.
Nam Da-reum, it's time to go home.
Wake up. Nam Da-reum.
This is driving me nuts.
What do I do?
Huh?
This is crazy.
I must be crazy.
I'm crazy!
Oh, seriously.
I think I'm going to throw up.
What? You and the CEO did...
- You slept with him?
- No!
No, I fell asleep in the CEO's office.
Right, there is no way
my confucian girl would do that.
But why on earth did you go there?
I do not know.
I think I went into zombie mode again.
There is a picture of Chan in there.
- Not a photoshoot, a natural one.
- You are nuts.
Please, get a handle
on that drinking habit. For real.
Da-reum, I'm telling you
because you make things so hard for me.
I'm sorry.
I'm really not drinking anymore, for real.
Good grief!
But you didn't cause more trouble
in the CEO's office, right?
Probably...
I guess so?
What... I have a bad feeling about this.
- I don't know.
- Don't tell me, you...
Did you black out?
Yeah.
Ms. Nam Da-reum.
- Good morning.
Whoa, Nam Da-reum!
Hey, I saw a new side of you yesterday.
You just took this,
went like this, and pop!
The bottle cap spun right off,
flew over there, and bam!
One of a kind.
- High-five.
- Huh?
M-me? What did I do? Why...
What's going on?
- Da-reum, you were so cool yesterday.
- Huh?
Da-reum, you're the best.
Good morning!
Good morning.
- Da-reum.
- Yes?
Did you get home okay?
You seemed drunk when you left early.
Yes.
- He's so handsome.
- Nam Da-reum.
Nam Da-reum.
What? What is this memory?
I think the CEO was there.
Um, Team Leader.
- Yes?
- Has the CEO come in?
The CEO?
I think he stayed up all night
at the office again.
He did?
Shoot, what's going on?
What could have happened
for him to be looking at me?
Remember, please. Think, think, think.
Come on, Da-reum.
SAMPLE ROOM
Hey, looks like someone's still hungover.
Da-reum. Oh, there you are.
- Are you feeling okay?
- Yes.
I was really drunk yesterday, wasn't I?
- I didn't make mistakes yesterday, did I?
- Huh? Mistakes?
Mistakes? What mistakes? You left early,
what mistakes could you have made?
Oh, Da-reum. It's too bad you couldn't
stay longer yesterday.
I mean, Director Lee Chan
even came at the end,
and it was incredible.
What?
Whoa, what a surprise.
I mean, I thought
he was just good-looking,
but his personality is great too.
Look. He took a picture just with us
to congratulate us
for joining the company.
Chan came?
But, um... here at the company,
he's Director...
Shouldn't you call him Director?
Wait a minute.
I guess Da-reum is a fan of DNX.
- Right?
- Oh.
I mean, I almost made the mistake
of just saying,
"It's Lee Chan!" yesterday too.
Oh my.
Da-reum, what's wrong?
Is it because of what I said?
No, it's not.
It's nothing.
Getting drunk...
Crawling into the CEO's office to sleep.
I didn't even get to see Chan.
What's the point of living, Nam Da-reum?
Just die. Just drop dead.
It was finally my chance to see him.
Yikes!
Ms. Nam Da-reum,
why do you call for your mom
when you see me?
Um, about yesterday...
I'm sorry, CEO.
I remember getting drunk
and going into your office,
but when I woke up, it was morning.
You don't remember?
How convenient
that you never seem to remember.
- What?
- Never mind.
It's probably for the best.
I was going to send you home
once you sobered up,
but you were too drunk to wake up.
Then,
what about you, CEO?
I...
I left after working.
Of course. What a relief.
I was worried I kept you from leaving.
Please be more careful in the future.
Behavior like that...
can give people the wrong idea.
Yes.
I'm sorry, CEO.
I'll make sure it never happens again.
Yes, Team Leader.
Da-reum, go to the first-floor showroom
and help them tidy up.
Yes, yes.
My team leader told me
to go to the showroom,
so I should get going.
Ms. Nam Da-reum.
What? Why is he following me?
The miracle I'd hoped for desperately...
didn't happen on a special day,
but in the middle of a very ordinary one.
At a totally unexpected moment.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
CHEON SEON-AE
EPILOGUE
Scrub, with love.
Scrub the grime from the heart.
Even the grime in every corner.
I'll scrub it away for you.
Scrub, scrub. With love.
The bruises on your heart...
even the bruises on your heart,
I will scrub away with love.
Scrub, scrub.
- Oh my, CEO!
- Um...
- No, good morning, ma'am.
- My, you pulled an all-nighter again?
- Go get some sleep.
- No...
I'll be done in a flash.
No, it's all right.
I have papers spread out everywhere.
Goodness, don't mind me.
If you still have work to do, go ahead.
I'll be out of your hair in a jiffy.
- Huh?
- Ma-Ma'am.
Ma-Ma'am, ma'am, Ms. Cheon!
Would you...
like to have a cup of coffee with me?
Coffee? A morning coffee sounds great.
Scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub.
Scrub the grime.
- Nice to meet you, Da-reum.
- How do you know my name?
This isn't a dream, is it?
Overseas Training for Top Employees?
I get the sense
she's intentionally getting close to me.
CEO, oh my. CEO, you're amazing.
You don't think she's a honey trap
sent by Director Kim, do you?
- Call me.
- See you!
Are they dating? Our CEO and Chan?
No way!